export const letters = [
    {
        letter: 'a',
        questions: [{question: 'Variable that stores multiple values', answer: 'array'}, {question: 'Value passed to a function', answer: 'argument'}, {question: 'Set of programming instructions', answer: 'algorithm'}],
        state: {gotRight: false, gotWrong: false, passed: false}
    },
    {
        letter: 'b',
        questions: [{question: 'True or false', answer: 'boolean'}, {question: 'Don\'t forget this in your switch statement', answer: 'break'}, {question: 'The project was harder than this question', answer: 'bingo'}],
        state: {gotRight: false, gotWrong: false, passed: false}
    },
    {
        letter: 'c',
        questions: [{question: 'Your webpage would look ugly without it', answer: 'css'}, {question: 'Template used to create objects in JavaScript', answer: 'class'}, {question: 'Function passed as an argument into another function', answer: 'callback'}],
        state: {gotRight: false, gotWrong: false, passed: false}
    },
    {
        letter: 'd',
        questions: [{question: 'What we aspire to be after the bootcamp', answer: 'developer'}, {question: 'Statement used to check if your code works', answer: 'debugger'}, {question: 'JavaScript expression that makes it possible to unpack values from arrays, or properties from objects, into distinct variables', answer: 'destructuring'}],
        state: {gotRight: false, gotWrong: false, passed: false}
    },
    {
        letter: 'e',
        questions: [{question: 'What you get when you try to reassign a constant variable', answer: 'error'}, {question: 'How JavaScript interacts with HTML', answer: 'events'}, {question: 'JavaScript standard intended to ensure the interoperability of webpages across different browsers', answer: 'ecmascript'}],
        state: {gotRight: false, gotWrong: false, passed: false}
    },
    {
        letter: 'f',
        questions: [{question: 'Block of code that returns a value', answer: 'function'}, {question: 'You can use this instead of a for loop', answer: 'foreach'}, {question: 'Returns the largest integer less than or equal to a number', answer: 'floor'}],
        state: {gotRight: false, gotWrong: false, passed: false}
    },
    {
        letter: 'g',
        questions: [{question: 'Knows everything', answer: 'google'}, {question: 'Scope in which variables can be accessed from anywhere', answer: 'global'}, {question: 'Functions that can be exited and later re-entered', answer: 'generator'}],
        state: {gotRight: false, gotWrong: false, passed: false}
    },
    {
        letter: 'h',
        questions: [{question: 'The structural base of a webpage', answer: 'html'}, {question: 'The Document Metadata element in HTML', answer: 'head'}, {question: 'Default behavior of moving all the declarations to the top of the scope before code execution', answer: 'hoisting'}],
        state: {gotRight: false, gotWrong: false, passed: false}
    },
    {
        letter: 'i',
        questions: [{question: 'The best coding school', answer: 'isdi'}, {question: 'Refers to the position of the elements in an array', answer: 'index'}, {question: 'This loop will break your system', answer: 'infinite'}],
        state: {gotRight: false, gotWrong: false, passed: false}
    },
    {
        letter: 'j',
        questions: [{question: 'Object-oriented programming language that is not JavaScript', answer: 'java'}, {question: 'Creates and returns a new string by concatenating all of the elements in an array', answer: 'join'}, {question: 'Syntax based upon JavaScript syntax for serializing objects, arrays, numbers, strings, booleans, and null', answer: 'json'}],
        state: {gotRight: false, gotWrong: false, passed: false}
    },
    {
        letter: 'k',
        questions: [{question: 'Reserved word that is part of the syntax in a programming language', answer: 'keyword'}, {question: 'Method that returns the property names of an object', answer: 'keys'}, {question: 'CSS at-rule that controls the intermediate steps in an animation sequence', answer: 'keyframes'}],
        state: {gotRight: false, gotWrong: false, passed: false}
    },
    {
        letter: 'l',
        questions: [{question: 'Used to perform repeated tasks based on a condition', answer: 'loop'}, {question: 'Property that refers to the number of elements in a given array', answer: 'length'}, {question: 'HTML label that defines a list element', answer: 'li'}],
        state: {gotRight: false, gotWrong: false, passed: false}
    },
    {
        letter: 'm',
        questions: [{question: 'Method that calls a function on all elements of an array and creates a new array', answer: 'map'}, {question: 'CSS property that defines the space on all sides of an element', answer: 'margin'}, {question: 'Built-in JS object that has properties and methods for mathematical constants and functions', answer: 'math'}],
        state: {gotRight: false, gotWrong: false, passed: false}
    },
    {
        letter: 'n',
        questions: [{question: 'The intentional absence of a value', answer: 'null'}, {question: 'A loop in a loop', answer: 'nested'}, {question: 'Library that is used for running web applications outside the client\'s browser', answer: 'nodejs'}],
        state: {gotRight: false, gotWrong: false, passed: false}
    },
    {
        letter: 'o',
        questions: [{question: '(Almost) everything in JavaScript', answer: 'object'}, {question: 'The sort() method does this with the values of an array', answer: 'order'}, {question: 'Defines the transparency level of an element in CSS', answer: 'opacity'}],
        state: {gotRight: false, gotWrong: false, passed: false}
    },
    {
        letter: 'p',
        questions: [{question: 'Method to ask for user input', answer: 'prompt'}, {question: 'Variable that is attached to an object', answer: 'property'}, {question: 'Mechanism by which JavaScript objects inherit features from one another', answer: 'prototype'}],
        state: {gotRight: false, gotWrong: false, passed: false}
    },
    {
        letter: 'q',
        questions: [{question: 'Common keyboard layout', answer: 'qwerty'}, {question: 'What your program does when you cancel a prompt', answer: 'quit'}, {question: 'The <q> tag in HTML', answer: 'quote'}],
        state: {gotRight: false, gotWrong: false, passed: false}
    },
    {
        letter: 'r',
        questions: [{question: 'To get a value from a function', answer: 'return'}, {question: 'A webpage that looks good on all devices', answer: 'responsive'}, {question: 'Type of function that calls itself', answer: 'recursive'}],
        state: {gotRight: false, gotWrong: false, passed: false}
    },
    {
        letter: 's',
        questions: [{question: 'Zero or more characters written inside quotes', answer: 'string'}, {question: 'Your question has probably been asked on here already', answer: 'stackoverflow'}, {question: 'Operator that only requires three dots', answer: 'spread'}],
        state: {gotRight: false, gotWrong: false, passed: false}
    },
    {
        letter: 't',
        questions: [{question: 'Operator that checks the type of a value', answer: 'typeof'}, {question: 'JavaScript operator that takes three operands', answer: 'ternary'}, {question: 'Strongly typed programming language that builds on JavaScript', answer: 'typescript'}],
        state: {gotRight: false, gotWrong: false, passed: false}
    },
    {
        letter: 'u',
        questions: [{question: 'When you forget to assign a value to a variable', answer: 'undefined'}, {question: 'Method used to add an item to the beginning of an array', answer: 'unshift'}, {question: 'Universal character encoding standard', answer: 'unicode'}],
        state: {gotRight: false, gotWrong: false, passed: false}
    },
    {
        letter: 'v',
        questions: [{question: 'Var, let or const', answer: 'variable'}, {question: 'How we check if a user fills in a form field correctly', answer: 'validation'}, {question: 'JavaScript framework for building user interfaces', answer: 'vuejs'}],
        state: {gotRight: false, gotWrong: false, passed: false}
    },
    {
        letter: 'w',
        questions: [{question: 'Type of loop used to repeat a specific block of code until a condition is met', answer: 'while'}, {question: 'Object on which we call prompts and alerts', answer: 'window'}, {question: 'What getDay() gives you in a number', answer: 'weekday'}],
        state: {gotRight: false, gotWrong: false, passed: false}
    },
    {
        letter: 'x', 
        questions: [{question: 'Better not name your variable this', answer: 'x'}, {question: 'Markup Language used to transport and save data', answer: 'xml'}, {question: 'Agile software development methodology that takes "best practices" to extreme levels', answer: 'xp'}],
        state: {gotRight: false, gotWrong: false, passed: false}
    },
    {
        letter: 'y',
        questions: [{question: 'Output of the getFullYear() method', answer: 'year'}, {question: 'Color represented by #FFFF00', answer: 'yellow'}, {question: 'Keyword used to pause and resume a generator function', answer: 'yield'}],
        state: {gotRight: false, gotWrong: false, passed: false}
    },
    {
        letter: 'z',
        questions: [{question: 'Developer who has not slept for 3 nights solving a bug', answer: 'zombie'}, {question: 'The index of the first element in an array', answer: 'zero'}, {question: 'CSS property that sets the order of a positioned element and its descendants', answer: 'z-index'}],
        state: {gotRight: false, gotWrong: false, passed: false}
    }
    ];